=Summer in Love=
= الصيف في الحب =
=Episode 2= (Good To See You Again)
= الحلقة 2 = (من الجيد رؤيتك مرة أخرى)
Shi Yi,
شي يي ،
what's wrong with you today?
ما هو الخطأ معك اليوم؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It's good to see you.
من الجيد رؤيتك.
Exam is coming.
الامتحان قادم.
Are you nervous?
هل انت متوتر؟
I feel like you're
أشعر وكأنك
different today.
مختلف اليوم.
We're getting late.
نحن نتأخر.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Okay.
تمام.
Sit tight.
اجلس بثبات.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
(This time,)
(هذا الوقت،)
(fate is in my own hand.)
(المصير في يدي.)
The questions are so hard.
الأسئلة صعبة للغاية.
Shi Yi!
شي يي!
Xia He!
شيا هي!
Why is she so excited?
لماذا هي متحمسة جدا؟
(Experimental Middle School) (2008 Hanjiang High School Exam Venue)
(المدرسة الإعدادية التجريبية) (مكان امتحان مدرسة هانجيانج الثانوية لعام 2008)
(Hanjiang High School)
(مدرسة هانجيانغ الثانوية)
Sit tight.
(مدرسة هانجيانغ الثانوية) اجلس بثبات.
(The second exam day)
(يوم الامتحان الثاني)
(If I remember correctly,)
(إذا كنت أتذكر بشكل صحيح،)
(father met an accident at this time.)
(تعرض الأب لحادث في هذا الوقت).
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Shanshan.
شانشان.
Yang Xin?
يانغ شين؟
I've bought this for you.
لقد اشتريت هذا لك.
Exam is over.
انتهى الامتحان.
Let's go out.
لنخرج.
If you take the flower,
إذا أخذت الزهرة ،
you'll lose your value.
ستفقد قيمتك.
The flower is still blooming.
الزهرة لا تزال تتفتح.
Yet you're dumped.
ومع ذلك ، فقد هُجرت.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Are you in love with me?
هل أنت تحبني؟
You don't want to see us together?
ألا تريدين رؤيتنا معًا؟
You're so shameless as usual.
أنت وقح كالمعتاد.
Wait.
انتظر.
(Hanjiang High School)
(مدرسة هانجيانغ الثانوية)
Look.
ينظر.
If you had agreed,
إذا كنت قد وافقت ،
you'll be just one of them.
ستكون واحدًا منهم فقط.
I have to say,
يجب أن أقول،
you're already
أنت بالفعل
a player at your age.
لاعب في عمرك.
Yang Xin,
يانغ شين ،
who do you think I, Gao Shanshan, am?
من برأيك أنا جاو شانشان؟
Wait.
انتظر.
Shanshan!
شانشان!
It serves you right.
أنها تخدم لك الحق.
You've embarrassed me in front of everyone.
لقد أحرجتني أمام الجميع.
I'll not forgive you.
لن اسامحك.
What?
ماذا؟
Don't you touch her!
لا تلمسها!
Let go!
اتركه!
Apologise to her.
اعتذر لها.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
I'm looking for my father.
أبحث عن والدي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I won't let this slide!
لن أدع هذه الشريحة!
Hello, Biao.
مرحبا بياو.
Come here quickly.
تعال الي هنا بسرعة.
I was bullied.
لقد تعرضت للتخويف.
I think the sound comes from there.
أعتقد أن الصوت يأتي من هناك.
It's my father's factory.
إنه مصنع والدي.
Why did it happen earlier?
لماذا حدث ذلك في وقت سابق؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Today's my high school exam.
اليوم هو امتحان مدرستي الثانوية.
Father didn't go to work.
الأب لم يذهب إلى العمل.
He went to save others.
ذهب لإنقاذ الآخرين.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
There's second explosion.
هناك انفجار ثان.
Did you bring your phone?
هل أحضرت هاتفك؟
No.
لا.
I can't bring a phone to exam.
لا يمكنني إحضار هاتف للاختبار.
Hurry.
عجل.
I need to stop my father.
أنا بحاجة لإيقاف والدي.
You can't run away after beating me.
لا يمكنك الهروب بعد ضربي.
Stop right there.
توقف هناك.
We're running out of time.
نحن نفاد الوقت.
Stay here!
ابق هنا!
I have no time for you now.
ليس لدي وقت لك الآن.
You've embarrassed me in front of everyone.
لقد أحرجتني أمام الجميع.
And you have no time for me now.
وليس لديك وقت لي الآن.
Aren't you shameless?
ألست وقح؟
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Scram!
انصرف!
Shouldn't you
لا يجب عليك
apologise for what you did?
أعتذر عما فعلته؟
You can go nowhere.
لا يمكنك الذهاب إلى أي مكان.
Stay away from her!
ابقى بعيدا عنها!
Do you think I'm scared of you?
هل تعتقد انني خائف منك؟
You beat me again?
هل هزمتني مرة أخرى؟
I've never been bullied like that!
لم أتعرض للتنمر من هذا القبيل!
I'll never forgive you!
أنا لن يغفر لكم!
What?
ماذا؟
Shi Yi!
شي يي!
- Go now! - Let go of me!
- اذهب الآن!  - ترك لي!
- Xia He! - Shi Yi!
- شيا هي! - شي يي!
Run!
يجري!
- Run! - Where are you going?
- يجري!  - إلى أين تذهب؟
(All the best.)
(أتمنى لك كل خير.)
(Shi Yi,)
(شي يي)
(save your father.)
(حفظ والدك.)
This is funny.
هذا مضحك.